Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 3: Boxes 45-52 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 3: Boxes 45-52
- Working Families Party (WFP), 2000-2005; Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 67: 8 Points on the Election, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. December 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 68: Today's Election, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 69: Building Power, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 70: Sunday Evening at 10 o'clock, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 71: WFP Update: One Bright Spot in a Sea of Darkness, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. November 3, 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 72: WFP Update: The Hidden Winner, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. November 17, 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 73: WFP Update: This Time We Mean It, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. December 7, 2004. Item is in English.
- Working Families Party (WFP), 2006-2009; Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: NY Post Attacks Working Families, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. February 9, 2009. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Budget Fight - Forward this Video, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. March 9, 2009. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Let the Middle-Class Pay?, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. January 8, 2009. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Mr. Springsteen, Mr. Seeger, Mr. Lincoln, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. January 20, 2009. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: 158,891, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. December 16, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: An iTunes tax?, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. December 18, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Finally., Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. November 4, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: It's Wednesday, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. November 5, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Obama on WFP Line and Other Results, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. November 21, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Vote Change - Like You Mean It!, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. October 22, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Term Limits - Barack - and Beyond, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. October 28, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Do More With Your Vote, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. October 30, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Working Families for Obama Poster Contest, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. September 2, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: "Primary" Opportunities - Tomorrow, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. September 8, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: This one's a treat, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. September 11, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Bailout?, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. September 22, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Bailout -- Toledo, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. September 29, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Universal Healthcare - But How?, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. May 27, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: End of an Era, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. July 2, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Cleaning Up Albany - the big news you haven't heard, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. July 15, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Wrong Answer, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. August 13, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Victory!, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. August 20, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Economic Stimulus?, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. May 8, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: What Could Have Benn/What Can Still Be - Reflections on Spitzer, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. March 13, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: The New York State Budget, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. April 4, 2007. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Weather Bad Enough For You?, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. April 19, 2007. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: NY Post Attacks Working Families, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 28: Budget Fight - Forward This Video, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 29: Let the Middle-Class Pay?, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 30: Mr. Springsteen, Mr. Seeger, Mr. Lincoln, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 31: 158,891, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 32: An iTunes tax?, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 33: 5 More Votes, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. November 1, 2008. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Finally., Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 35: It's Wednesday in America, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 36: Obama on WFP Line and Other Results, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 37: Term Limits - Barack - and Beyond, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 38: Do More With Your Vote, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 39: Working Families for Obama Poster Contest(Win a Grand), Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 40: "Primary" Opportunities - Tomorrow, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 41: This One's a Treat, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 42: Bailout?, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 43: The Bailout -- Holy Toledo, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 44: Universal Healthcare - but how?, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 45: End of an Era, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 46: Cleaning Up Albany, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 47: The Wrong Answer, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 48: Victory!, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 49: Economic Stimulus?, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 50: What Could Have Been/What Can Still Be - Reflections on Spitzer, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 51: The New York State Budget, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 52: Weather Bad Enough For You?, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 53: Loosen their grip, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    By Dan Cantor. February 20, 2008. Item is in English.
- British Labor Bids for Power by Scott Nearing, 1926; Publication (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Historic Scarboro Conference of the Trades Union Congress, Publication (Box 50, Folder 19)
    By Scott Nearing. Item is in English.
- Basic Criteria Used in Wage Negotiations by Sumner H. Slichter, 1947; Publication (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Basic Criteria Used in Wage Negotiations, Publication (Box 50, Folder 20)
    By Sumner H. Slichter. Item is in English.
- Basic Criteria Used in Wage Negotiations by Sumner H. Slichter, 1947; Publication (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Basic Criteria Used in Wage Negotiations, Publication (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Struggle for Revolutionary Socialism by Heinrich Ehrlich, 1934; Publication (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Struggle For Revolutionary Socialism, Publication (Box 50, Folder 22)
    By Heinrich Ehrlich. Item is in English.
- How Do The Communists Work by Victor Feather, 1953; Publication (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: How Do the Communities Work, Publication (Box 50, Folder 23)
    By Victor Feather. Item is in English.
- Poor Old Competition by Stuart Chase, Publication (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Poor Old Competition, Publication (Box 50, Folder 24)
    By Stuart Chase. Item is in English.
- C.I.O. Labor's New Challenge by Will Herberg, Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The C. I. O. Labor's New Challenge, Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
    By Will Herberg. Item is in English.
- Wanted: A New Deal in Place of the Racketeering in Workmen's Compensation by Estelle Lauder, 1934; Publication (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Wanted: A New Deal In Place of The Racketeering in Workmen's Compensation, Publication (Box 50, Folder 26)
    By Estelle Lauder. Item is in English.
- International Council of Trade and Industrial Unions by A. Losovsky, Publication (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The International Council of Trade and Industrial Unions, Publication (Box 50, Folder 27)
    By A. Losovsky. Item is in English.
- A Letter to American Workers by V.I. Lenin, 1934; Publication (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: A Letter to American Workers, Publication (Box 50, Folder 28)
    By V. I. Lenin. August 20, 1918. Item is in English.
- How Class Collaboration Works by Bertram D. Wolfe, Publication (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: How Class Collaboration Works, Publication (Box 50, Folder 29)
    By Bertram D. Wolfe. Item is in English.
- Case for the Guaranteed Annual Wage by Mary T. Waggaman, 1948; Publication (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: The Case for the Guaranteed Annual Wage, Publication (Box 50, Folder 30)
    By Mary T. Waggaman. August 16, 1948. Item is in English.
- Letters to Judd: An American Workingman by Upton Sinclair, Publication (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Letters To Judd: An American Workingman, Publication (Box 50, Folder 31)
    By Upton Sinclair. Item is in English.
- Ethical Aspects of Social Insurance by Louis F. Buckley, Publication (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Ethical Aspects of Social Insurance, Publication (Box 50, Folder 32)
    By Louis F. Buckley. Item is in English.
- Problems of Organized Labor Today by William Z. Foster, 1946; Publication (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Problems of Organized Labor Today, Publication (Box 50, Folder 33)
    By William Z. Foster. Item is in English.
- Organizing Methods in the Steel Industry by Wm. Z. Foster, 1936; Publication (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Organizing Methods in the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 50, Folder 34)
- War Crisis: Questions and Answers by Wm. Z. Foster, 1940; Publication (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: The War Crisis: Questions and Answers, Publication (Box 50, Folder 35)
- American Labor Movement by Jay Lovestone, Publication (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: The American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 50, Folder 36)
    By Jay Lovestone. Item is in English.
- Industrial Unionism by Wm. Z. Foster, 1936; Publication (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Industrial Unionism, Publication (Box 50, Folder 37)
- What Means a Strike in Steel by William Z. Foster, 1937; Publication (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: What Means A Strike In Steel, Publication (Box 50, Folder 38)
- Communist Manifesto by Karl Marx and Frederick Engels, Publication (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Communist Manifesto, Publication (Box 50, Folder 39)
    By Karl Marx and Frederick Engels. Item is in English.
- Wage-Labour and Capital by Karl Marx, 1933; Publication (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Wage-Labour and Capital, Publication (Box 50, Folder 40)
    By Karl Marx. Item is in English.
- No Friend of Labor by James Morton Freeman, 1948; Publication (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: No Friend of Labor, Publication (Box 51, Folder 1)
    By james Morton Freeman. Item is in English.
- Why and Whither of Labor Unions by the RT. Rev. Msgr. Francis J. Haas, Publication (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Why and Whither of Labor Unions, Publication (Box 51, Folder 2)
    By Francis J. Haas. Item is in English.
- Meet the Man Who Plans to Rule America by Joseph P. Kamp, 1958; Publication (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Meet the Man Who Plans To Rule America, Publication (Box 51, Folder 3)
    By Joseph P. Kamp. Item is in English.
- Meet the Man Who Plans to Rule America by Joseph P. Kamp, 1958; Publication (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Meet the Man Who Plans to Rule America, Publication (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Trade Unions Since the N.R.A. By Nathaniel Honig, 1934; Publication (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Trade Unions Since the N.R.A, Publication (Box 51, Folder 5)
    By Nathaniel Honig. Item is in English.
- Trade Unions Since the N.R.A. by Nathaniel Honig, 1934; Publication (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Trade Unions Since the N.R.A, Publication (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Communists and the Trade Unions by Roy Hudson, 1943; Publication (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Communists and the Trade Unions, Publication (Box 51, Folder 7)
    By Roy Hudson. Item is in English.
- Labor and the N.R.A. By Lois Macdonald, 1934; Publication (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Labor and the N.R.A, Publication (Box 51, Folder 8)
    By Lois Mac Donals; Gladys L. Palmer; Theresa Wolfson. Item is in English.
- Sit-Down by Joel Seidman, 1937; Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: "Sit-Down", Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
    By Joel Seidman; Robert Morss Lovett. Item is in English.
- Sit-Down by Joel Seidman, 1937; Publication (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Sit-Down, Publication (Box 51, Folder 10)
    By Joel Seidman. Item is in English.
- A Labor Party for America? By Joel Seidman, 1936; Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: A Labor Party For America?, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
- C.S. Case Against Labor by Michael Quin, Publication (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The C. S. Case Against Labor, Publication (Box 51, Folder 12)
    By Michael Quin. Item is in English.
- What is the Catholic Attitude by William J. Smith, S.J., Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: What is the Catholic Attitude on Big Industry Corporatism Liberalism Communism Fascism Democracy Race and Color Labor, Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
    By William J. Smith, S. J. Item is in English.
- Unions and the Socialist by Leo Krzycki, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Unions and the Socialists, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    By Leo Krzycki. Item is in English.
- Union-Smashing in Sacramento: The Truth About The Criminal Syndicalism Trial by Herbert Solow, 1935; Publication (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Union-Smashing in Sacramento: The Truth About the Criminal Syndicalism Trial, Publication (Box 51, Folder 15)
    By Herbert Solow. August 1935. Item is in English.
- Shall Labor Support Roosevelt? By Norman Thomas, 1936; Publication (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Shall Labor Support Roosevelt?, Publication (Box 51, Folder 16)
    By Norman Thomas. Item is in English.
- Shall Labor Support Roosevelt? By Norman Thomas, 1936; Publication (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Shall Labor Support Roosevelt?, Publication (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Heritage of Gene Debs by Alexander Trachtenberg, Publication (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Heritage of Gene Debs, Publication (Box 51, Folder 18)
    By Alexander Trachtenberg. Item is in English.
- History of May Day by Alexander Trachtenberg, 1935; Publication (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The History of May Day, Publication (Box 51, Folder 19)
- Trade Union Unity League: Its Program, Structure, Methods and History, Publication (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Its Program, Structure, Methods, and History, Publication (Box 51, Folder 20)
    By The Trade Union Unity League. Item is in English.
- American Labor Movement: An Outline by Leo Wolman, 1927; Publication (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The American Labor Movement: An Outline, Publication (Box 51, Folder 21)
    By Leo Wolman. Item is in English.
- American Labor Movement: An Outline by Leo Wolman, 1927; Publication (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 51, Folder 22)
- Rights of Man Are Worth Defending, 1942; Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Rights of Man are Worth Defending, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
    By Roger Baldwin; Zechariah Chafee; Melvyn Douglas; William Green; Phillip Murray; A. Philip Randolph, Joseph Schlossberg. Item is in English.
- Catholic and His Union by Norman C. McKenna, 1948; Publication (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Catholic and His Union, Publication (Box 51, Folder 24)
    By Norman C. McKenna. Item is in English.
- Open Shop by Clarence S. Darrow, 1904; Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Open Shop, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    By Clarence S. Darrow. Item is in English.
- Is Communism Un-American? By Eugene Dennis, 1947; Publication (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Is Communism Un-American? 9 Questions About the Communist Party Answered, Publication (Box 51, Folder 26)
    By Eugene Dennis. Item is in English.
- Is Communism Un-American? By Eugene Dennis, 1947; Publication (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Is Communism Un-American? 9 Questions About the Communist Party Answered, Publication (Box 51, Folder 27)
- Dimitroff: Working Class Unity-Bulwark Against Fascism, 1935; Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Working Class Unity-Bulwark Against Fascism, Publication (Box 51, Folder 28)
    By Dimitroff. Item is in English.
- Dimitroff: Working Class Unity-Bulwark Against Fascism, 1935; Publication (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Working Clas sUnity-Bulwark Against Fascism, Publication (Box 51, Folder 29)
    By The Congress of Struggle for Unity of the Working Class. Item is in English.
- Lizzie Likes Her Job by Prof. John R. Commons, 1920; Publication (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Lizzie Likes Her Job, Publication (Box 51, Folder 30)
    By John R. Commons. Item is in English.
- Democratic Front by Earl Browder, 1938; Publication (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: The Democratic Front, Publication (Box 51, Folder 31)
    By Earl Browder. May 28,1938. Item is in English.
- 1940 Elections: How the People Can Win by Earl Browder, 1939; Publication (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: The 1940 Elections: How The People Can Win, Publication (Box 51, Folder 32)
    By Earl Browder. May 6 to 8, 1939. Item is in English.
- How Do We Raise the Question of a Labor Party? By Earl Browder, Jack Stachel, 1935; Publication (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: How Do We Raise the Question of a Labor Party?, Publication (Box 51, Folder 33)
    By Earl Browder; Jack Stachel. Item is in English.
- Social and National Security by Earl Browder, 1938; Publication (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Social and National Security, Publication (Box 51, Folder 34)
    By Earl Browder. December 3,4,5, 1938. Item is in English.
- Social Insurance by Grace M. Burnham, 1932; Publication (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Social Insurance, Publication (Box 51, Folder 35)
    By Grace M. Burnham. Item is in English.
- Concentration of Wealth by Henry Laurens Call, 1907; Publication (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: The Concentration of Wealth, Publication (Box 51, Folder 36)
    By Henry Laurens Call. December 27, 1906. Item is in English.
- Threat to the Labor Movement: The Conspiracy Against the Trade Unions by William F. Dunne, Publication (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The Threat to the Labor Movement, Publication (Box 51, Folder 37)
    By William F. Dunne. Item is in English.
- For Revolution by V.F. Calverton, 1932; Publication (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: For Revolution, Publication (Box 51, Folder 38)
    By V.F. Calverton. Item is in English.
- Case Against David Dubinsky by William Weinstone, 1946; Publication (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: The Case Against David Dubinsky, Publication (Box 51, Folder 39)
    By William Weinstone. Item is in English.
- Should the Workers Form a Party of Their Own?: A Debate by Charney Vladeck, 1932; Publication (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Should The Workers Form a Party of Their Own?, Publication (Box 51, Folder 40)
    By Morris Hillquit; Matthew Woll. Item is in English.
- Industrial Socialism by William D. Haywood, Publication (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Industrial Socialism, Publication (Box 51, Folder 41)
    By William D. Haywood; frank Bohn. Item is in English.
- NRA and American Labor by Will Herberg, 1932; Publication (Box 51, Folder 42)
- Great San Francisco General Strike by Wm. F. Dunne, 1934; Publication (Box 51, Folder 43)
- Present Trends in the Clerical Occupations by Grace L. Coyle, 1928; Publication (Box 51, Folder 44)
- A Letter to American Workers by V.I.. Lenin, 1934; Publication (Box 51, Folder 45)
- Organizing Methods in the Steel Industry by Wm. Z. Foster, 1936; Publication (Box 51, Folder 46)
- Bankruptcy of the American Labor Movement by Wm. Z. Foster, Publication (Box 51, Folder 47)
- Wrecking the Labor Banks by Wm. Z. Foster, 1927; Publication (Box 51, Folder 48)
- Unionizing Steel by Wm. Z. Foster, 1936; Publication (Box 51, Folder 49)
- Red Baiting: enemy of Labor by Louis Budenz, 1937; Publication (Box 51, Folder 50)
- Save Your Union: The Meaning of the "Anti-Trust" Persecution of Labor by Louis F. Budenz, Publication (Box 51, Folder 51)
- Next Emancipation by James O'Neal, 1929; Publication (Box 51, Folder 52)
- Representation in Industry by John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1918; Publication (Box 51, Folder 53)
- Colorado Industrial Plan by John d. Rockefeller, Jr., 1916; Publication (Box 51, Folder 54)
- Collection Bargaining by John W. Scoville, Publication (Box 51, Folder 55)
- We, People of America: And How We Ended Poverty, A True Story of the Future by Upton Sinclair, Publication (Box 51, Folder 56)
- People's Front Illusion by Jay Lovestone, Publication (Box 51, Folder 57)
- People's Front Illusion by Jay Lovestone, Publication (Box 51, Folder 58)
- Spying on workers by Robert W. Dunn, 1932; Publication (Box 51, Folder 59)
  photo-copy
- Problems of Organized Labor Today by William Z. Foster, 1946; Publication (Box 51, Folder 60)
- People's Press - v.1-2 (1936-1937) [incomplete], Publication (Box 51, Folder 61)
- Corlears Hook: Slum Clearance Plan Under Title I of the Housing Act of 1949, 1951; Publication (Box 51, Folder 62)
  January 1951
- The Right to Security: A Survey of New Plans by Orlie Pell, 1943; Publication (Box 51, Folder 63)
- (Legal orientation), Publication (Box 52)
  - Connecticut Federation of Labor Bulletin: vol. 1, no. 12 - vol. 2, no. 12, 1947-1948; Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
    June 1947 - July 1948
  - Connecticut Federation of Labor Bulletin: vol. 3, no. 1 - vol. 3, no. 13, 1948-1949; Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
    September 1948 - September/October 1949
  - Connecticut Federation of Labor Bulletin: vol. 3, no. 14 - vol. 4, no. 6, 1949-1950; Publication (Box 52, Folder 3)
    November 1949 - July/August 1950
  - Connecticut Federation of Labor Bulletin: vol. 4, no. 7 - vol. 5, no.15, 1950-1951; Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
    September/October/November 1950 - December 1951
  - Illinois Central Railroad, 1910; Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Rail Services Planning Office, 1974-1975; Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - National Mediation Board, 1968; Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Amendment to Railroad Retirement Act of 1937, 1958; Publication (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - War Manpower Commission, 1945; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1973; Publication (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - National Employment Law Project, 2017; Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Jobs With Justice Education Fund, 2017; Publication (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Ruskin College, Oxford, 1984; Publication (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations, 1960; Publication (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Text digitized from the collection., Publication (Box 9999)